A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 417)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Chrome (S. 1868)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Ex-POWs--Benefits
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Reconstruction--Viet Nam
    - Government Operations Committee
    - House Administration
    - House Administration--Appropriations
    - House Internal Security
    - Interior Committee (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 418)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interior Committee (3 folders)
    - Interior Committee--Land Use (H.R. 10294)
    - Interior Committee--Vitamins
    - Interior Committee--Kyros Vitamin Bill (H.R. 16317)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 419)
  - Committees [and General Legislation]
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (2 folders)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Alaska Pipeline
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Appropriations
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Emergency Energy Act (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 420)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Mandatory Fuel Allocation
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Railroad Pensions
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Strip Mining
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Strip Mining (H.R. 11500)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Vitamins (H.R. 643)
    - I and II, 1974 (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 421)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--III, 1974 (2 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 422)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Abortion I and II.
      Note: This folder contains graphic anti-abortion literature.
    - Judiciary Committee--Appropriations
    - Judiciary Committee--Black Power
    - Judiciary Committee--Equal Rights Amendment--Opposition
    - Judiciary Committee--Guns
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayer
    - Judiciary Committee--Nixon--Amnesty
    - Judiciary Committee--Nixon--Impeachment (2 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee--Nixon--Post-resignation (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 423)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Nixon--Post-resignation (1 folder)
    - Judiciary Committee--Seniority--Evans Resolution
    - Judiciary Committee--Veterans Day, November 11
    - Legislation--General (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 424)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Legislation--National Land Use Legislation
    - Legislation--Recess Reply
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
      Note: Merchant Marine and Fisheries material is on microfilm; see list in folder.
    - Post Office (2 folders)
    - Post Office--Appropriations
    - Post Office--Pay Raise
    - Post Office--2nd Class Mail (H.R. 4128)
    - Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities--Watergate
    - Public Works (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 425)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Public Works (1 folder)
    - Rules Committee (2 folders)
    - Committee on Small Business
    - Science and Astronautics (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 426)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Science and Astronautics--Space Science and Applications
    - Science and Astronautics--Appropriations
    - Science and Astronautics--NASA
    - Science and Astronautics--NASA Budget Material
    - Veterans Affairs Committee
    - Veterans Affairs Committee--Appropriations
    - Veterans Affairs Committee--World War I
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 427)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee (5 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 428)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee (6 folders)
    - Ways and Means Committee--Depreciated Gifts
    - Ways and Means Committee--Gas Tax
    - Ways and Means Committee--Highway Trust Fund
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 429)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee--Pension Reform (2 folders)
    - Ways and Means Committee--Revenue Sharing
    - Ways and Means Committee--Social Security
    - Ways and Means Committee--Social Security--Medicaid
    - Ways and Means Committee--Tax Policy Review Act (H.R. 15230)
    - Ways and Means Committee--Veterans
    - Ways and Means Committee--Youth Employment Funds
  - Federal Installations.
    - Assateague National Seashore (2 folders)
    - Back Bay National Wildlife Refuge
    - Barrier Islands of Virginia--Eastern Shore
    - Chincoteague Refuge
    - Colonial National Historical Park, Yorktown (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 430)
  - Federal Installations.
    - Fisherman's Island
    - NASA--Langley AFB
    - NASA--Space Radiation Effects Lab
    - Parramore Island Coast Guard Station
    - VA Center, Hampton
  - General Files.
    - Accomack County
    - Achievements
    - Department of Agriculture (2 folders)
    - Air Force
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 431)
  - General Files.
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission [ARBC]
    - AMTRAK (4 folders)
    - Appointments
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 432)
  - General Files.
    - Agriculture--Raymond H. Womble
    - Department of the Army (2 folders)
    - Atomic Energy Commission [AEC]
    - Cape Charles
    - Bureau of the Census
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation
    - Chesapeake Corporation
    - Chincoteague
    - Chincoteague Ponies
    - Civil Aeronautics Board [CAB]
    - Civil Defense
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 433)
  - General Files.
    - Cleveland Aquarium--Roger Zucker
    - Coast Guard (2 folders)
    - Coile, Forrest
    - Commerce Department--General (2 folders)
    - Commerce Department--Nansemond Petro Chemical
    - Consumer
    - Corps of Engineers (2 folders)
    - Customs
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 434)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--General (4 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 435)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--General (1 folder)
    - Department of Defense--Army National Guard
    - Department of Defense--Association of the U.S. Army [AUSA]
    - Department of Defense--Camp Peary
    - Department of Defense--Cape Charles Air Force Station
    - Department of Defense--Cheatham Annex
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 436)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--CONARC
    - Department of Defense--Dahlgren Naval Weapons Lab
    - Department of Defense--Fort Eustis (3 folders)
    - Department of Defense--Fort Eustis--AAVLABS (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 437)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--Fort Eustis--AAVLABS (1 folder)
    - Department of Defense--Fort Monroe (3 folders)
    - Department of Defense--Closing of Fort Monroe
    - Department of Defense--Fort Story
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 438)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--Langley Air Force Base (2 folders)
    - Department of Defense--Langley AFB Hospital
    - Department of Defense--Military Traffic Management and Terminal Service (MTMTS)
    - Department of Defense--POW/MIA
    - Diplomatic Letters, 1973
    - Eastern Shore Railroad (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 439)
  - General Files.
    - Economic Development Administration
    - Environmental Protection Agency [EPA]
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Air Pollution
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Water Pollution (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 440)
  - General Files.
    - Equal Employment Opportunity [EEO]
    - Essex County
    - Farmers Home Administration [FHA]
    - Federal Aviation Administration [FAA] (2 folders)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation [FBI]
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]
    - Federal Energy Office [FEO]
    - Federal Energy Office--Inquiries (2 folders)
    - Federal Energy Office--Cases
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 441)
  - General Files.
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Maritime Commission
    - Federal Power Commission [FPC]
    - Federal Trade Commission [FTC]
    - General Services Administration [GSA] (2 folders)
    - Gloucester County
    - Gloucester-Mathews Soil Condition--Waste Treatment System
    - Government Accounting Office [GAO]
    - Hampton, City of (2 folders)
    - Hampton Roads, Port of
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 442)
  - General Files.
    - Health, Education and Welfare [HEW] (5 folders)
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Office of Education in Virginia (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 443)
  - General Files.
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Office of Education in Virginia (1 folder)
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Education Estimates in Va. Schools
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Food and Drug Administration [FDA] (2 folders)
    - HEW--National Cancer Institute
    - HEW--National Institutes of Health
    - HEW--Public Health Service [PHS]
    - Virginia Department of Highways
    - Hopesville Ranch, Inc.
    - House of Representatives
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 444)
  - General Files.
    - Housing and Urban Development [HUD] (3 folders)
    - Inaugural Committee, 1973
    - Department of the Interior (2 folders)
    - International Development Association
    - Interstate Commerce Commission [ICC]
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 445)
  - General Files.
    - Interstate Commerce Commission--Penn Central to Cape Charles
    - James City County
    - Department of Justice
    - King George County
    - King William County
    - Department of Labor (2 folders)
    - Lancaster County
    - Maps
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD] (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 446)
  - General Files.
    - Mathews County
    - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy
    - National Academy of Sciences [NAS]
    - NASA
    - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration [NOAA]
    - National Park Service
    - National Science Foundation
    - Department of the Navy (2 folders)
    - New Kenty County
    - Newport News, City of
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 447)
  - General Files.
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company (2 folders)
    - Northumberland County
    - Oceanography
    - Office of Economic Opportunity [OEO]
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness
    - Office of Management and Budget
    - Office Interns, 1973
    - Old Dominion College
    - Patrick Henry Airport
    - Patronage
    - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce
    - Phoebus, Town of
    - Post Office Department
    - Postal Service--Commemorative Stamps
    - Richmond County
    - Seaford Sewage Treatment Plant
    - Selective Service System
    - Department of State
    - Tangier Island
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 448)
  - General Files.
    - Thomas Nelson Community College
    - Transportation Department (2 folders)
    - Treasury Department
    - United States Capitol
    - Veterans Administration [VA]
    - Commonwealth of Virginia (4 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 449)
  - General Files.
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company [VEPCO]
    - Virginia General Assembly
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science [VIMS]
    - Virginia Military Institute [VMI]
    - Virginia Port Authority
    - Virginia Seafood Council
    - Virginia Beach, City of
    - Wage and Price Freeze (2 folders)
    - Warsaw, Town of
    - Westmoreland County
    - Wetlands File
    - White House--Pardon--Support Nixon
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 450)
  - General Files.
    - White House--Pardon--Against
    - College of William and Mary
    - Colonial Williamsburg, Inc.
    - York County
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-May 1973 (9 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 451)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, June-December 1973 (7 folders)
    - Invitations Declined, January-March 1973 (4 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 452)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, April-September 1973 (6 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 453)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, October-December 1973 (4 folders)
    - NASA Invitations, 1973
    - Invitations--General, 1973
    - Invitations Accepted, January-March 1973
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 454)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, April-December 1974 (15 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 455)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, January-May 1974 (6 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 456)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, June-November 1974 (6 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 457)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, December 1974
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Major Legislative Accomplishments for the 1st Session of the 93rd Congress
    - Clean Elections Act of 1973 (P.L. 93-443) (2 folders)
    - Colonial National Historical Park--Access Rights Debt (P.L. 93-477)
    - Colonial National Historical Park--Increases Funds (P.L. 93-477)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 458)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Confirmation of Director of Office of Management and Budget
    - Dismal Swamp/Wildlife Refuge (P.L. 93-402)
    - Energy Policy Council (P.L. 93-275; P.L. 93-438) (2 folders)
    - Energy Legislation (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 459)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Endangered Species (P.L. 93-205)
    - Farmers Home Administration Emergency Loan Program (P.L. 93-24)
    - Fire Prevention and Control (P.L. 93-498)
    - Fishing Industry--National Support for Strong Program
    - Geothermal Energy--Demonstrations (P.L. 93-410)
    - Health Programs Extension Act of 1973 (P.L. 93-45)
    - Interstate Highways (P.L. 93-61)
    - Israel--Aid--Phantoms (P.L. 93-199)
    - Jewry--Freedom of Emigration in East-West Trade (P.L. 93-618)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 460)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Lobster--Continental U.S. Ownership of Homarus American (P.L. 93-242)
    - Marine Protection, Research, and Sanctuaries Act of 1972--Amend
    - Markers for Statuary Hall
    - Merchant Marine--Conversion of Vessels to Unsubsidized Service
    - Merchant Marine Act of 1936--Amend Section 502(a) (P.L. 93-71)
    - Missing in Action--Vietnam
    - National Sea Grant College and Program Act of 1966 (P.L. 93-73)
    - National Space Week, 1-7 October 1973
    - Oil Pollution Act--Amendment (P.L. 93-119)
    - Rural Environmental Assistance Program (REAP) (P.L. 93-86)
    - Rural Electrification Act (P.L. 93-32)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 461)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Solar Energy Demonstration (P.L. 93-409)
    - Veterans--Cemeteries and Burial Allowance (P.L. 93-43)
    - Veterans Disability and Death Pensions (P.L. 93-177; P.L. 93-527)
    - War Powers (P.L. 93-148)
    - Coastal Zone Management Act (P.L. 93-612)
    - Cyprus--Halt U.S. Aid to Turkey (P.L. 93-448)
    - Repeal of Daylight Savings Time (P.L. 93-434)
    - Intercoastal Shipping Act of 1933--Amendment (P.L. 93-487)
    - Marine Protection, Research, and Sanctuaries Act of 1972 (Ocean Dump)
    - NASA Authorization (P.L. 93-316)
    - National Hunting and Fishing Day (P.L. 93-424)
    - National Science Foundation Authorization (P.L. 93-413)
    - Opium Ban--Negotiations with Turkey
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 462)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Solar Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Act of 1974
    - Aircraft--Kidnapping by Seizing (P.L. 93-366)
    - Economic Development Administration (P.L. 93-46)
    - Maritime Authorizations (P.L. 93-70)
    - Public Health Service Hospitals (P.L. 93-165) (4 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 463)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Public Health Service Hospitals (2 folders)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Adoption of Child--Deduction of Expenses
    - USS Arizona
    - Balance of Payments
    - Blacksburg/Metallurgy Research Center
    - Chesapeake Bay Compact
    - Governor's Land Archaeological District
    - Conversion Research
    - Cost of Existence Index
    - Cyprus--Withdrawal of Foreign Troops
    - Debts Overdue from Foreign Governments
    - Dismal Swamp--Monument
    - Earth Resources Technology Satellite
    - Education of Handicapped
    - Environmental Policy Act of 1969--Amendment
    - Export-Import Bank Credit to Russia
    - Federal Crime to Kill/Assault Fireman or Law Enforcement Officer
    - Ferry Farm
    - Fertilizer--Ban Exports
    - Fiscal Year to Coincide with Calendar Year--Federal Government
    - American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 464)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Forest Conservation and Improvement Act of 1973
    - General Information File, 93rd Congress
    - Government Contracts--Reports to Congress (H.R. 12416)
    - Import Restrictions--Fisherman's Protective Act of 1967
    - Intermodal Transportation
    - Israel--Massacre of School Children
    - Labor Violence at Construction Site
    - Jurisdiction of Lorton Penal Facility
    - McCabe, Frank J.--Relief
    - Merchant Marine Academy--Allow Daughters from Canal Zone
    - Monetary Penalty--Transportation of Merchandise
    - Merchant Marine Act of 1970--Amend Section 40(b)
    - Ministers--Tax Credit for Retirement
    - Middle East
    - Milk Price Support at 85% of Parity
    - Maritime Authorizations for FY75
    - Mineral Rights--Grant to Coastal States
    - NASA--Automobile Engine Development
    - NASA--Weather Phenomena Research Program
    - Nuclear Power Plants Siting Procedures
    - Nuclear Vessel Incentive Support Program
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 465)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Olympic Committee Proceedings
    - Paperwork Burden
    - Panama Canal--Retain Sovereignty and Jurisdiction
    - Pesticides (2 folders)
    - Petroleum Products--Franchised Dealers
    - Pious Puffin--Permit Vessel to be Documented
    - Possible Legislation
    - Pollution
    - Predatory Animals
    - Railroad Lines--Prevent Abandonment
    - Shenandoah National Park--Designated Wilderness Area
    - Social Security--Disability for the Blind
    - Tax Exemption--Civil Service Employees Working in Combat Zone (H.R. 17321)
    - Tourism--Energy Impact
    - Unknown Soldier--Vietnam
    - National Volunteer Fireman Day
    - Watergate Special Prosecutor
    - Wildlife Restoration
    - Busing--Constitutional Amendment to Prohibit (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 466)
  - Master Files.
    - First Session, A-H (9 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 467)
  - Master Files.
    - First Session, I-S (12 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 468)
  - Master Files.
    - First Session, T-Z (7 folders)
    - Second Session, A-F (7 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 469)
  - Master Files.
    - Second Session, G-R (13 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 470)
  - Master Files.
    - Second Session, S-Z (8 folders)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Downing, January-August 1973
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 471)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Downing, September-December 1973 (4 folders)
    - General, January-December 1973 (12 folders)
    - Downing, January-September 1974 (9 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 472)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Downing, October-December 1974 (3 folders)
    - General, January-December 1974 (12 folders)
    - News Releases (3 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 473)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Photographs (2 folders)
  - Political Files.
    - Byrd for Vice President
    - Clippings--State General Elections, 1973
    - TND's Campaign, 1974
    - Campaigns and Elections Other than TND
    - Contributions to TND's Campaign
    - Contribution Letters, 1974
    - Finance Committee--TND's Campaign, 1974
    - Friends and Nice Letters
    - General Files (2 folders)
    - Godwin
    - Campaign Helpers
    - Local Democratic Party and Elections
    - King William County
    - Lancaster County
    - Middlesex County
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 474)
  - Political Files.
    - Campaign Materials
    - National Democratic Party and Elections
    - Newport News, City of
    - Northumberland County
    - Political Opponents
    - Public Inquiry of Financial Disclosure
    - Petitions, 1974
    - Information Regarding Campaign Receipts
    - Requests for Political Information
    - State Democratic Party and Elections
  - Post Office Files, 92nd and 93rd Congresses.
    - B-E (A omitted) (4 folders)
    - General Information (2 folders)
    - G
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 475)
  - Post Office Files, 92nd and 93rd Congresses.
    - H-R (I and L omitted) (9 folders)
    - Star Routes
    - S-Y (X and Z omitted) (6 folders)
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files, January-November 1973 (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 476)
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files, December 1973-November 1974, undated (3 folders)
    - Dedications
    - Speeches on Congress--Duties, etc.
    - Armed Forces Speeches
    - Commencement Addresses
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 477)
  - Speech Files.
    - General Legislation Speeches
    - Historical Speeches
    - Maritime Speeches
    - Patriotic Speeches
    - Political Speeches
    - Space Committee Speeches
    - Miscellaneous Speeches
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 478)
  - Speech Files.
    - Merchant Marine Speech Information File
    - Space Speech Information File
    - Speech Material (2 folders)
    - Extension of Remarks
  - Voting Record.
    - 1972-1974 (1 folder)
    - 1973-1974 (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 479)
  - [Military] Academies.
    Note: Military Academy Files are restricted and cannot be served.
    - Class Entering in 1975, Adkins-Surry (47 envelopes)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 480)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Class Entering in 1975, Taylor-Witten (11 envelopes)
    - Class Entering in 1976, Adams-Royals (58 envelopes)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 481)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Class Entering in 1976, Selnau-Young (20 envelopes)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Committee on Aging
    - Agriculture Committee (2 folders)
    - Agriculture Committee--Food Stamps
    - Agriculture Committee--Monongahela National Forest (H.R. 12503)
    - Agriculture Committee--Rice Bill
    - Appropriations (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 482)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Appropriations (2 folders)
    - Appropriations--Agriculture and Related Agencies
    - Appropriations--Defense
    - Appropriations--HUD--Independent Agencies
    - Appropriations--Labor--Health, Education, and Welfare
    - Appropriations--Interior
    - Appropriations--State, Justice, Commerce, and Judiciary
    - Appropriations--Public Works
    - Appropriations--Transportation
    - Appropriations--Treasury, Postal Service, General Government
    - Appropriations--Interior Subcommittee--Chincoteague
    - Armed Services Committee (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 483)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Armed Services Committee (2 folders)
    - Armed Services Committee--Seapower Subcommittee--Shipyards
    - Armed Services Committee--Shipyards Hearing
    - Armed Services Committee--George Willis
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 484)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Banking and Currency
    - Banking and Currency--Inflation
    - Banking, Currency and Housing (3 folders)
    - Banking, Currency and Housing--Financial Institutions Act Amendment (H.R. 7474)
    - Banking, Currency and Housing--Financial Reform Act (H.R. 13077)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 485)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].